ALEXANDER VAUGHAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

An aspiring Developer with 2+ years of experience with Web development, Linux, and Java Mobile apps.

Someone who takes pride in learning and expanding their skill set every day, to better help achieve the goals of the project and team around him

CONTACT

Phone:

313-720-0142

Email:

avaughan11@gmail.com

https://github.com/Alkarin

Linkedin:

http://bit.ly/2kgociK

Location:

San Diego, USA

SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5 • CSS/CSS3 JavaScript jQuery AngularJS 5
- Git
- Linux
 - Java

- PHP
- MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Developer

Barefoot Solutions - San Diego | Jan 2017 - Present

- Deployed and pushed live production updates to client server environments, including custom Linux troubleshooting and scripting to optimize ease of team development
- Developed and implemented feature sets and bug fixes for Android Mobile Apps and Web based projects for dozens of clientele including government regulated projects and health care devices
- Built fully functioning, responsive and visually pleasing Web pages based on technical docs and design mock-ups for Wordpress, AngularJS and PHP served web pages
- Redid the company site, check it out! http://bit.lv/2Bwb3fP

Software Developer Intern

Barefoot Solutions - San Diego | July 2016 - Dec 2016

- QA and bug ticketing on Code Deliveries and feature sets for client projects across multiple browsers and devices
- Implemented bug fixes for Web and Android applications
- Identified and resolved data implementation issues for LAMP stack projects, while handling production sensitive data

EDUCATION

Southwestern College

Computer Science GPA 3.0 | 2017 - Present

• Computer Organization and architecture Went in depth into CPU design, including various C and MIPS Assembly projects to communicate with the CPU

San Diego Mesa College

Computer Science GPA 4.0 | 2015 - 2016

- Intro Java Programming
- Data Structures and Algorithms in Java

Lynda and Udemy Courses

Constantly learning new skills via online courses such as

- PHP with MySQL Beyond the Basics (Lynda)
- Git Essentials {Lynda}
- Angular 5 The Complete Guide (Udemy)